<resources>
  <string name="app_name" translatable="false">FiveSpace</string>
  <string name="space_image_activity">Space details</string>
  <string name="earth_rotation">
    The Earth\’s rotation is gradually slowing.

    This deceleration is happening almost imperceptibly, at approximately 17
    milliseconds per hundred years, although the rate at which it occurs is not
    perfectly uniform. This has the effect of lengthening our days, but it
    happens so slowly that it could be as much as 140 million years before the
    length of a day will have increased to 25 hours.
  </string>
  <string name="hottest_planet">
    The hottest planet is not the closest planet to the Sun.

    Even though Mercury is the closest planet to the Sun, it is not actually the
    hottest. Mercury does not have any atmosphere meaning that this planet is
    only hot in the daytime when it is directly facing the Sun. At this stage
    temperatures can rise to 425°C but at night the planet\’s temperature can
    drop down to a freezing -180°C. Venus is the hottest planet. Its thick
    clouds trap the Sun\’s heat causing Venus to be a sizzling 500°C all of the
    time!
  </string>
  <string name="voyager1">
    The furthest manmade object is Voyager 1. It has messages for aliens
    on-board.

    In 1977, Voyager 1 and 2 were launched. Their primary mission was to visit
    Jupiter and Saturn. Voyager 2 continued onto Uranus and Neptune; Voyager 1
    has now made its way into interstellar space. Voyager 1 is further away from
    Earth than the distance between the Sun and Pluto. Both craft carry a golden
    record on board, which will act like a time-capsule of Earth. It has
    greetings from Earth as well as different kinds of music. It also has noises
    of rocket engines, the sea, people talking, animal\’s sounds and lots of
    images. All of which sum up the Earth. United States President Jimmy Carter
    said at the time \“This record represents our hope and our determination,
    and our good will in a vast and awesome universe.\” These messages have been
    recorded as electronic impulses which can be translated into written words.
    If any aliens find it then can enjoy some Louis Armstrong as well some
    Peruvian panpipes!
  </string>
  <string name="mars">
    On Mars the Sun appears about half the size as it does on Earth.

    At the closest point to the Sun, the Martian southern hemisphere leans
    towards the Sun, causing a short, intensely hot summer, while the northern
    hemisphere endures a brief, cold winter: at its farthest point from the Sun,
    the Martian northern hemisphere leans towards the Sun, causing a long, mild
    summer, while the southern hemisphere endures a lengthy, cold winter.
  </string>
  <string name="moon">
    The dark side of the moon is a myth.

    In reality both sides of the Moon see the same amount of sunlight however
    only one face of the Moon is ever seen from Earth. This is because the Moon
    rotates around on its own axis in exactly the same time it takes to orbit
    the Earth, meaning the same side is always facing the Earth. The side facing
    away from Earth has only been seen by the human eye from spacecraft.
  </string>
</resources>
